it happened so fast
I got up and started screaming at her
calling her an idiot
but my parents asked me to take it easy
and she said it was a joke
and she didn't think I'd react so intensely
my aunt remained seated
and my cousin asked me to calm down
and drink some water
but I grabbed my stuff
and as I was getting ready
I told my sister
she was getting $0 for her dream wedding dress
then I walked out
I heard louder commotion as I walked in
my dad and cousin followed me outside
trying to talk
but I asked to be left alone
my and dad spoke to
saying I was too harsh on my sister over a joke
and said that I know this is how she is
with her dark sense of humour
they said she's been crying
after I decided to back out of helping her
and said this ruin her wedding
they want me to reconsider my decision
since it might damage my relationship with my sister
but I refused
did I overreact info
it's my aunt that would usually bring up what happened
from time to time
and say stuff like if what happened didn't happen
you would have had at least 2 kids now
or do you know what day it is
your wedding anniversary
it's harsh but she stopped doing it anymore
maybe my sister is being influenced by her
but still it hurt the same
and more coming from my own sister